SZYMON KASPRZAK 07516 961 054 / s.kasprzak8@gmail.com

Personal profile

I am a highly motivated IT professional with 4 years' experience in a wide range of IT related technologies, used to working in fast paced environments to tight deadlines. I have a methodical approach to my work with excellent attention to detail, all combined to provide effective and efficient systems. I am highly motivated, and customer focused, with an exemplary attendance and time-keeping record.

Always keen to learn, I look to gain knowledge from those around me, and to pass on that knowledge to others, and I also commit myself to learning away from the workplace to enhance my skill set.

Skills

- M365, Azure, & O365 application management
- Window 10, MacOS, and Linux administration
- Network management of both wired and wireless LANs, including design and deployment
- Security focused mindset including ISO27001 and GDPR
- Strong analytical, problem-solving and organisational skills
- Adaptable to change, absorb pressure, and able to resolve and overcome issues methodically
- Can operate both as an individual and as a team member
- Working on both short-term issues and long-term projects

Professional experience

May 2018 - Present Workplace: AppLearn Role: IT Support Analyst

Responsibilities:

- Administration of Microsoft 365 Active Directory, O365, InTune MDM, OneDrive, Exchange, SharePoint, Teams
- Installing, configuring and troubleshooting endpoints Windows 10, Mac OS, Ubuntu
- Support, installation and maintenance of all wired/wireless LAN infrastructure and VPNs, including switches, routers, & access points – Ubiquiti Unifi & HP Aruba
- Managing VoIP infrastructure SNOM, Polycom, Packnet
- Managing G Suite
- Network printer installation, maintenance and troubleshooting
- Service Desk administration Jira
- Maintaining system documentation and asset registers Confluence & SharePoint
- Support both on-site and remote users
- Working to ITIL standards within agreed SLAs
- IT purchases and managing 3rd party relationships
- Providing and user training on all system and processes

June 2017 - May 2018

Work place: UCEN Manchester

Role: IT Technician Responsibilities:

- Assisting personnel with installation, configuration and ongoing usability of system hardware and software
- Offering daily operations and systems support to personnel/ students
- Verifying functionality of hardware and software components
- Troubleshooting hardware and software issues in person, remotely and via phone
- Assisting employees with computer problems and answering their questions
- Tracking work in progress and recording issues and solutions

June 2012 – August 2015 Work place: L'Oreal

Role: Warehouse Operative

Responsibilities:

- Completing customers' orders to a high quality in timely manner
- Working effectively as a member of an international team
- Fulfilling all duties in line with Health and Safety Regulations
- Training new employees
- Meeting targets on a daily basis

February 2009 - May 2011

Work place: Aquapark Polkowice RCRR S.A.

Role: IT Specialist Responsibilities:

- Solely responsible for configuring and troubleshooting desktops, laptops and servers across the organisation to strict deadlines
- Installing and updating new software to ensure a smooth running of all departments
- Administration of the company network and sale systems
- Promoting image of the company by updating and improving the web pages
- Implementing new programmes and training colleagues
- Providing technical support during special events
- Management of the backup system
- Assisting employees with IT related issues on a daily basis
- Operating/maintaining the company's CCTV and sound system

Education

September 2015 - June 2017

The Manchester Metropolitan University, Computer Network Engineering with Administration, Foundation Degree

Modules included:

- Linux Fundamental with Administration: 84%
- Networking with Routing & Switching: 94%
- Network Security and Software Management: 82%
- Professional and Academic Development: 76%
- Scaling & Connecting Networks in WAN: 92%
- Virtual Desktop Infrastructure: 85%
- Advanced Network Design with Security and Environmental Factors: 83%
- Practice-based Research: 83%

September 2007 - June 2011

Lower Silesia College of Entrepreneurship and Technology, Poland, Specialisation: Computer Systems and Networks, Engineer degree

Certifications

September 2019

CCNA Routing and Switching

May 2018

CCNA Cyber Ops

May 2016

Microsoft Technology Associate:

- Windows Server Administration Fundamentals
 - Security Fundamentals
- Networking Fundamentals

September - December 2015

South Tyneside College Professional and Vocational (an online course) Customer Service Level 2 (2015) NCFE

References

References are available on request